Guide to the Public Administration Reports and Studies (Assorted), 1910-1992 AIS.1996.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Reports on Municipal Governments in Pennsylvania, 1947-83; VI.
  - Oakmont, Part of a Master Plan Report, Item 11- Housing, 1958
  - Oakmont, Long Range Development Plan, 1959
  - O'Hara, Guide for Action, Planning, Procedures, and Programs, Undated
  - O'Hara, Comprehensive Plan, 1965
  - Ohio, Planning, Administration, and Financing, 1962
  - Orbisonia-Rockhill, Industrial Survey for Orbsonia-Rockhill, Pennsylvania, 1954
  - Penn, Traffic Analysis of Proposed East Crossroads Shopping Center, Undated
  - Penn, Master Plan, 1962 (Box 32)
  - Penn Hills, Land Use Policy Plan, 1978
  - Penn Hills, A Recreation and Open Space Plan, 1970
  - Perry County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Potter County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Pottstown, Statistical Abstract of Pottstown, Pennsylvania, 1958
  - Pike County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Pittston, Statistical Abstract of Pittston, Pennsylvania, 1957
  - Redstone, The Redstone Township Plan, Undated
  - Rostraver, Guide for Action: Supplemental Document to the Comprehensive Plan, 1966
  - Saint Clair, Master Plan, 1959
  - Scottdale, Guide for Action, Undated
  - Scranton and Dunmore, Statistical Abstract of Scranton and Dunmore, Pennsylvania, 1958
  - Sewickley, District Plan, 1947
  - Shannon, Amendment to the Comprehensive Development Policy Plan, 1968
  - Shannon, Central Area Plan, 1956
  - Sharon, Comprehensive Sharon Core Area Design Concept & Development, 1972
  - Sharon, Statistical Abstract of Sharon, Pennsylvania, 1953
  - Sharon, Sketch Design Study of Sharon Riverbank, 1973
  - Shenango Valley, Comprehensive Plan: History, Population, Land Use, and Physical Background, Undated
  - Snyder County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Snyder County, Revised Subdivision and Land Development Ordinance, 1980
  - Somerset County, A Statistical Abstract, 1954
  - Somerset County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Springfield, Springfield Area Background Analysis and Comprehensive Land Use Plan, 1976
  - State College, Statistical Abstract of State College, Pennsylvania, 1954
  - Sullivan County, Recreation and Open-Space Plan, 1971
  - Susquehanna County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Susquehanna County, Recreation and Open-Space Plan, 1971
  - Susquehanna County, Flood Plain Management and Protection, 1975
  - Swissvale, Statistical Abstract of Swissvale, Pennsylvania, 1953
  - Swissvale, Preliminary Redevelopment Project, 1980
  - Tarentum, Pattern for Progress, Community Housing & Planning Associates, 1954
  - Tioga County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Tioga County, Recreation and Open-Space Plan, 1971
  - Titusville, Report on Existing Methods for the Collection and Disposal of Garbage and Other Refuse Together With an Analysis of Rate Structures, 1951 (Box 33)
  - Union County, Water Resources Plan for Union County, 1979
  - Union County, Energy Study, 1978
  - Union County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Union County, Open Space and Recreation Plan Update, 1977
  - Union County, Surface Runoff and Sedimentation Study for Union and Snyder Counties, 1977
  - Union County, Historic Preservation Plan, 1977
  - Uniontown, Central Business District Plan (Oversize), 1968 (Box 38)
  - Uniontown, Statistical Abstract of Uniontown, Pennsylvania, 1953 (Box 33)
  - Uniontown, A Prospectus and Work Program Uniontown-Connellsville Area Transportation Study, 1968
  - Uniontown, Comprehensive Plan, 1957
  - Uniontown, City of Uniontown Police Department Administrative Study, 1968
  - Unity, Development Plan and Proposals, 1966
  - University City, Redevelopment Potentials and University Interests, 1963
  - Venango County, Annual Report, Venango County Planning Commission, 1979
  - Venango County, Municipal Planning Manual, Undated
  - Venango County, Industrial Analysis, 1969
  - Venango County, Industrial Analysis: Site Development Cost, 1969
  - Venango County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Venango County, Handicapped Opportunities: An Evaluation, 1980
  - Versailles, The Campaign for a Better Form of Municipal Government in North Versailles Township, 1963
  - Warren County, Development of a Self-Supporting Transportation System to Serve a Rural Area: Concept and Implementation, 1970
  - Warren County, Recreation Plan, 1970
  - Warren County, Highway Program in and for the County of Warren, 1970
  - Washington County, Environmental Statement on Cross Creek Watershed, 1973
  - Washington County, Peters Township Planning Program, 1970
  - Washington County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Washington County, The Highway Program, 1970-1976
  - Washington County, Economic Growth Center Stucy, 1973
  - Washington County, Mine Drainage Pollution, 1968
  - Washington County, Proposed Ordinances, 1975
  - Washington County, Proposed Mobile Home and Mobile Home Park Ordinances, 1971
  - Washington, Comprehensive Plan, 1970
  - Washington, Background for Planning, Undated
  - Washington, Central Business District: A Development Plan, 1962
  - Washington, Statistical Report of Washington, Pennsylvania, 1952
  - Wayne County, County Data Book, 1982 (Box 34)
  - Waynesburg, Comprehensive Plan, Report Number Two, Undated
  - Waynesburg, Comprehensive Plan, 1970
  - West Brownsville, Comprehensive Plan Summary, 1967
  - West Brownsville, Planning, Administration, and Financing, 1967
  - West Chester, Statistical Abstract of West Chester, Pennsylvania, 1958
  - Westmoreland County, County Data Book, 1982
  - Westmoreland County, 1967 Session
  - Whitehall, Comprehensive Plan Development Procedures, 1968
  - Whitehall, Urban Renewal Recommendations, c1967
  - White Oak, Master Plan Report, Item 5- Schools, 1959
  - White Oak, Master Plan Report, Item 4- Economy, 1959
  - Wilkes-Barre, Statistical Abstract of Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1954
  - Wilkins, Capital Improvements Program, Undated
  - Wilkinsburg, Neighborhood Analysis, 1966
  - Wilkinsburg, Annual Report, Wilkinsburg Borough Planning Commission, 1983
  - Wilkinsburg, Central Business Area Rehabilitation Study, 1963
  - Wilkinsburg, Neighborhood Analysis, 1966
  - Wilkinsburg, Comprehensive Plan, 1976
  - Wilkinsburg, A Review of Progress Under the Workable Program for Community Improvement for the Elimination and Prevention of Slums and Blight, 1963
  - Wilkinsburg, Statistical Abstract of Wilkinsburg, Pennsylvania, 1953
  - Wilkinsburg, An Internship Report, 1973
  - Wilkinsburg, Urban Renewal Project Planning Report One, 1962
  - Wilkinsburg, Summary Report of the Master Plan, c1959
  - Wyoming County, Recreation and Open Space Plan, 1971
  - York County, Highway Commercial Development, 1976
  - York County, Agricultural Land Preservation, 1975
  - York County, Storm Drainage Plan Study Design, 1976
  - York County, Erosion and Sedimentation Control, 1975
  - York County, Rural Social Services Study, 1978
  - York County, Comprehensive Sewerage Study, 1972
  - York County, Land Use and Land Value in Four Interchange Communities: An Interim Report on the York Study, 1966
  - Williamsport, Statistical Abstract of Williamsport, Pennsylvania, 1954
  - Williamsport, Central Business District Study, 1961
  - Windber, Recreational Study, 1977
  - Wyoming County, County Data Book, 1982
- Reports by the University of Pittsburgh, 1946-1977; VII.
  - Urban Studies: Some Questions of Outlook and Selection, 1960 (Box 39)
  - Career and Educational Opportunities in the Urban Professions, 1966
  - Urban Renewal in Metropolitan Context, 1959
  - Urban Renewal in Metropolitan Context, 1959
  - Public Administration 812: Public Policy Analysis, 1977
  - Non-Formal Educational Alternatives for Ethnic and Disadvantaged Groups: A Critically Annotated International Bibliography, 1972
  - Public Health Institute: Management Problems in Environmental Health II, 1965
  - Directory of Urban Planning Information Systems in the United States, 1968
  - Development Law for City and Regional Planners, 1963
  - Toward the Development of Citizen Participation in Neighborhood Preservation Policy, 1977
  - Critical Path of Urban Renewal, 1963
  - Tools and Techniques for Implementation of Urban Planning, 1967
  - The Production of Planners, Institute of Local Government, 1964
  - Patterns of Volunteering Activities in Standard Metropolitan Statistical Areas, 1976
  - Financing Higher Education through International Education, 1975
  - Intermodal Freight Transportation Coordination Problems and Potential, 1966
  - Refuse Collection and Disposal, 1946
  - Urban Studies: Some Questions of Outlook and Selection, 1960
  - Notes on Quantitative Methods in Urban and Regional Planning, 1976
  - Human Costs of Urban Renewal, 1964
  - Private Financing Considerations in Urban Renewal: A Report of the Proceedings of the Sixth Annual NAHRO Conference on Urban Renewal, 1961
  - Municipal Policy and Program Goals; An Advanced Course for Councilmen, Commissioners, and Supervisors, 1960
  - Reality Adjustment: A Young Institution Settles for Humane Care, 1964
  - International Air Transport: A Microsystem in Need of New Approaches, 1971
  - Urban Renewal: A Case Study in Emerging Goals in an Intergovernmental Setting, Undated
  - Institutional Requirements to Cope with Social Change in the United States, 1964
  - The University and the Community in the Domain of Health, 1971
- Reports from other States, 1960-1980; VIII.
  - Arizona, Tucson Area Transportation Study, Volume 1: An Inventory and Analysis of Existing Conditions (Oversize), 1960 (Box 38)
  - Arizona, Tucson Area Transportation Study, Volume 2: Forecasts and Plans (Oversize), 1980
  - California, Patterns on the Land: People, Open Space, Water, Money, Undated (Box 35)
  - Colorado, Commercial Development Along Arterial Streets, 1965
  - Florida, East Central Florida Commercial Development, 1965
  - Georgia, Organization and Methodology for River Basin Planning, 1964
  - Georgia, Development and Evaluation of Recommended Transportation System for the Atlanta Region, 1971
  - Georgia, Safer Streets in '72: Work Program for Five-Year Comprehensive Plan, 1971
  - Georgia, Safer Streets in '72, Appendices, 1971
  - Illinois, First Year Evaluation of the Illinois Urban High Crime Reduction Rate Program, Final Report, 1977
  - Illinois, Energy and Environment: An Intergovernmental Perspective, 1978
  - Illinois, Transportation System Plan Summary Description, 1974
  - Maryland, Environmental Impact Statement, Baltimore City, 1973
  - Massachusetts, Offshore Oil Development: Implications for Massachusetts Communities, 1976
  - New York, Industrial Specialization Among Urban Areas, 1975
  - New York, Land Use and Natural Resources Inventory, 1969
  - North Carolina, A Proposal for a Standardized Land-Use Classification System, Undated
  - Ohio, Comparative State Strip Mining and Reclamation Laws, 1965
  - Ohio, Land Site Investigations: Forecasts and Requirements to the Year 2000 for Second Phase of the Airport Feasibility Study for the Lake Erie Regional Transportation Authority, 1975
  - Rhode Island, Community Renewal Program for the City of Providence, 1964
  - Rhode Island, A Social Plan for Community Renewal of the City of Providence, 1964
  - Rhode Island, Schools, Master Plan Reports, 1963
  - Rhode Island, Zoning for East Providence, 1963
  - Rhode Island, Population: 1980, East Providence
  - Rhode Island, Parks, Recreation, and Open Space, Master Plan Reports, 1962
  - Rhode Island, Land Use Analysis and Physical Inventory, Master Plan Reports, 1962
  - Rhode Island, Master Plan for Land Use, 1962
  - Rhode Island, Master Plan for the City of Pawtucket, 1965
  - Tennessee, The Economic Impact of TVA, 1967 (Box 36)
  - Texas, Austin Tomorrow Comprehensive Plan, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Virginia, Interregional Planning of Water Resources Allocations by Systems Analysis Approach, 1974
  - Virginia, Solid Waste Disposal Study, 1978
  - Virginia, Master Plan of Land Use, Community Facilities, and Trafficways, 1964
  - Washington, Model Labor Contract Guide for Washington Cities, 1976
  - Washington (District of Columbia), Pennsylvania Avenue (Oversize), 1964 (Box 9)
  - West Virginia, Modeling Public Works Expenditures, 1970 (Box 36)
  - West Virginia, A Study of Food Acquisition of the Rural Elderly, 1970
  - West Virginia, Draft Environmental Statement and Land Management Plan for the Monongahela N.F. (National Forest), Undated
- Reports from Foreign Nations, 1972-1992; IX.
  - Denmark, Non-Offensive Defence No. 18, 1991
  - Denmark, Non-Offensive Defence No. 13, 1989
  - Denmark, Non-Offensive Defence & Conversion No. 19, 1991
  - Denmark, Non-Offensive Defence No. 12, 1989
  - Denmark, Non-Offensive Defence & Conversion No. 22, 1992
  - Egypt, Water and Wastewater Sector Institutional Support Program, 1988 (Box 36)
  - Egypt, Water and Wastewater Sector Institutional Support Program: Technical Annex II, c1985
  - Egypt, Water and Wastewater Sector Institutional Support Program: Technical Annex III, 1985
  - Egypt, Water and Wastewater Sector Institutional Support Program: Technical Annex I, c1985
  - Europe (Assorted), Washington (District of Columbia), Massachusetts, and New York, Rivers in the City, 1973
  - Japan, Tokyo's Financial History: A Century of Growth Amid Change, 1972
  - Sudan, The Myth of Decentralization: Centralization by Proxy, A Case Study of the Sudan, 1986
- Reports on Various Topics, 1949-1977; X.
  - Summary Report of the Second 1313 Conference on Redevelopment: Administrative Problems in Federal Aid for Urban Development and Redevelopment, 1949 (Box 37)
  - What Our Cities Need Most: Brains, The Case for Voluntary Support of Graduate Education in Urban Planning, Renewal, and Development, 1963
  - Major Labor-Law Principles Established by the NLRB and the Courts, December 1964-April 1970
  - Questions and Answers on Collective Bargaining: A Practitioner's Guide, 1977
  - Police Collective Bargaining, 1969
  - Bargaining Relations and Practices, 1968
  - Primer in Public Sector Labor Relations: A Practitioner's Guide, Undated
  - Public Sector Labor Legislation in the Midwest: A Practitioner's Guide, 1975
  - Questionnaire on the Execution of an Urban Renewal Program, 1959
  - Metropolitan and Urban Growth in the U.S.A.: 1900-1960, 1968
  - Managing Governments' Labor Relations, 1972
  - Trends in Industrial Location and Their Impact on Regional Economic Development: A Report on Research in Progress, 1969
  - The Coordination of Federal and State Coal Mine Health and Safety Programs with Special Reference to the Federal Coal Mine Health and Safety Act of 1969, 1971
  - Planning a Municipal Auditorium, 1955
  - The Westinghouse Transit Expressway: A New Concept in Rapid Transit for Metropolitan Areas, Undated
  - Energy and You: Solar Energy, 1977
  - Technique for Area Planning, 1967
  - Collective Bargaining and Public Administration, 1971
  - The Union View of Public Management's Responsibilities in Collective Bargaining, 1970
  - The Scope of Collective Bargaining in the Public Sector, 1971
  - Economic Development Manual, The Organization for Social and Technical Innovation, 1969
  - Delinquency Prevention and Organizational Relations, Undated
  - National Strategy to Reduce Crime, 1976
  - Crime Prevention Through Environmental Design Strategies and Directives, 1977
  - A Guide for Local Recreation Planning, 1970
  - Strike Preparation Manual, 1974